Jaime Luna C.

Software Developer

London, ON jaimelunaec@hotmail.com +593998080497

Software Engineer with more than 10 years of experience. Known for excellent troubleshooting skills, able to analyze code and good researcher of new technologies.

Always interested in apply the best practices and performance techniques to get better results in each used technology.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Software Developer Engineer

GTSOLUTIONS CIA. LTDA. - Quito, EC February 2018 to Present

Build mobile applications for Android and IOS using React-Native Help to maintain current websites using Visual Studio NET. Make queries to SQL Server Database

Software Development Leader

ROAD TRACK ECUADOR CIA. LTDA. - Quito, EC September 2007 to January 2018

Development and implementation of the vehicle localization web application. (Angular JS, HTML5, Bootstrap, C# for API provider, SQL Server, TFS)

Team Lead using scrum methods, code reviewer developed by other team members and responsible of assigning tasks.

Software Developer Senior

KLEINTOURS Y REPRESENTACIONES CIA. LTDA. - Quito, EC August 2005 to January 2007

Project Coordinator and Software Developer. (Visual Basic, SQL Server, Source Safe)

Education

Computer Systems Engineer in Computer Science

Pontificia Universidad Católica del - Ambato, EC 1995 to 2001

Skills

Angularjs (3 years), Javascript (5 years), Android Development (2 years), Microsoft SQL Server (4 years), Visual Studio (2 years), Google Analytics (2 years), Github (3 years), HTML5 (3 years), Bootstrap (2 years), Java (1 year), C# (2 years), Ionic Mobile (1 year), React-Native (2 years), React Js (1 year)

Links

https://ca.linkedin.com/in/jaime-luna-c-7022a968/en

https://systemblad.github.io/my-cv-web-pack

Certifications/Licences

Ultimate Angular 2 Developer with Bootstrap 4 & TypeScript

November 2016 to Present

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-7MW8MRUX/

Angular 2 is the latest development framework from Google that was just released on September 2016. Even though it is new, it is already a sought-after (& highly paid) skill for building scalable, robust and modern cross-platform applications.

Scrum Advanced: Software Development & Program Management

February 2017 to Present

https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-QZT56SKU/

Understand the detailed reasons for each scrum rule and how they help to deliver projects more effectively

JavaScript Online Test

July 2019 to Present

https://www.testdome.com/cert/abc3734ff8fa40669e15e1479b09b989

React JS Online Test

June 2019 to Present

https://www.testdome.com/cert/2b333ca7cefa44f489826c993fa90d59

Additional Information

Interests:

JavaScript Frameworks, HTML5, CSS3, Video games, Mobile native hybrid applications, Java Frameworks, Net Framework, Electric Vehicles.